- Hello.
- "Hey, boy wonder."
"Guess what I'm holding in my hand."
- Danny?
- "The one and only."
- "So how you doing?"
- Good. I'm good.
It's been a long time.
- How are you?
- Yeah. Good. Good.
Listen, I, uh...
I need your help.
"Units responding to the 187"
"at the K-Ram building
proceed with caution."
This is unit 1. We're moving in.
Freeze! Drop it!
Drop the weapon!
Turn around.
Hey, guys.
It's not what it looks like.
No, no, no, no. Y-you're going
about it all wrong, detective.
Y-you're coming straight out
of the gate with bad cop.
I mean, you do a good bad cop.
You are intimidating.
I'm not gonna--
I'm not gonna lie to you
but now let's bring good cop out.
He's nicer, more pleasant--
we build a rapport.
You-- maybe you say something like
"You thirsty?"
And I say "I'd love a cup of tea."
Here's another fine mess, eh?
They really found Jane
holding the murder weapon?
Yes, they did. Hightower twisted
some arms at Sac PD.
It's a joint investigation. We share
the sandbox but CBI is taking the lead.
I don't know why you're smiling.
Well, it's a new angle
at least, right?
I mean, he's never been
a murder suspect before.
We got an ID on the victim.
Landon Wale, 45.
He's some real estate mogul
from San Francisco.
What was he doing in Sacramento?
Well, office is a financial brokerage--
K-Ram investments, Inc.
Van Pelt's trying to locate the owner.
What's Jane say he was doing?
I-I was taking a walk
and--to get some air
and when I came by here I heard a shot
so, uh, I came to see if I could help
and that's when I discovered this man
lying here with the blood and--and no pulse.
He had the gun in his hand.
Yes, I confess. I-I picked it up.
I'm not good with forensics.
No, I can vouch for that.
He is, uh, terrible.
You heard a gunshot and ran in to help?
Yes, I did. I'm no hero.
I just did what any person
would do in that situation.
No one is calling you a hero.
Really? Okay.
Detective, how'd your guys catch this? 911?
Yeah. Uh, an anonymous call
said a man was murdered at this location.
- Did you make that call, Jane?
- No.
- Why would I do that?
- Hang on, boss.
This was stuck in his pocket.
Looks like a ruby.
A pretty nice one.
- Cool.
- Yeah, great.
Detective, could you uncuff
this one now, please?
He's still a suspect.
And he is not gonna leave town.
Release him into my custody.
You know he's not good for it.
Zero connection to the victim.
"Nada. Niente."
Zip.
"Naught."
I could go on.
I am reaching out to you, detective.
I know this man
and I know he's telling the truth
about what happened.
- The truth. Now.
- Beg your pardon?
Talk, or I will give you back
to Detective Reece. Seriously.
My wife's brother called me
and asked for my help.
He gave me this address
and when I got here
I found the dead guy. I guess
he called the police on me.
Your wife has a brother?
- Yeah. Danny Ruskin.
- Okay. Why'd he call the cops?
- Force my involvement.
- Why?
Well, either he didn't kill Landon Wale
and he wants me to help him
catch the real killer
or he did kill Landon Wale and he
wants me to help him elude justice.
- And you would do that for him?
- That's a very good question.
You know if the County Fair's
in town?
Mrs. Wale, what was
your husband's connection
to K-Ram Investments?
Where you found him?
I've never heard of it before today.
Me, neither and...
my brother and I were
business partners.
Real estate.
Landon was a good man.
Why would someone wanna hurt him?
We'll let you know.
And we understand
that Heather Rade is here?
Lan's assistant?
Upstairs.
Heather!
Concetta, honey...
People are bringing lots of food.
You don't need to do this.
No, I do. I need to keep busy.
I can't believe this is happening.
Yes, Melanie?
- Oh. The police?
- Yes, ma'am.
Did Mr. Wale ever speak to you
about a brokerage in Sacramento
- called K-Ram Investments?
- Sacramento?
Landon has a money guy here.
Sorry, no.
Mrs. Wale, did your husband
ever wear jewelry?
No.
We, uh, found this on him.
It's a Ruby. Half-carat.
Oh, my God. It's gone.
Why would Landon take it?
Landon gave me the statue
of Aphrodite on our honeymoon.
You know, Aphrodite...
The Greek goddess of love and sexuality.
Yes, ma'am.
It had rubies along the base.
I have a photo of it
for insurance purposes here.
How valuable is it?
It was worth over $200,000.
Well, you should file a claim.
Looks like the killer took it.
- Jane.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Jane?
County Fair starts Saturday.
- So Danny'll be there?
- Well, no. He's not that simple
but someone there will know where he is.
He's a carny like you used to be?
Uh, carny is a very
broad term, Lisbon.
Uh, Danny's more showbiz
but it's--it's been a while.
Before last night, when was
the last time you talked to him?
When I called him to tell him
what Red John had done.
Boss? K-Ram Investments
doesn't exist.
It's not registered
on any stock exchange.
- It's not even a real company.
- Who owns it?
A holding company
signed the lease.
I tracked that through three other outfits
to get to a Daniel Ruskin.
Daniel Ruskin. He got a sheet?
Long one. Got hooked for larceny
passing bad checks. Nothing violent.
Then was popped for fraud
two years ago in Toronto.
He's a con man, basically.
- Show business, eh?
- Well, confidence, game, showbiz--
it's a thin line.
So maybe the victim was a mark
in one of Danny's cons.
Vic finds out. They fight.
Danny kills him
and steals the statuette.
Possible. Danny is usually
smoother than that.
Right. Very smooth, the way
he forced you onto this case.
It's clever.
You're a pawn in his game.
I'm not a pawn. He...
Yeah? What?
Oh, you're very good.
You almost got me talking.
All right.
What are you keeping from me?
Nothing. He's family.
That's all.
- "Van Pelt."
- Complicated, right?
"Boss, it's Detective Reece for you."
- They got a call to Jane's phone
- It's for you.
- from the K-Ram offices.
- He's on his way over.
Stall him.
Stall him?
I didn't know your wife
was from this world, too.
Oh, yeah.
Her grandparents were carny royalty.
They ran big metal--
Ferris wheels, ghost trains.
They ran 'em all across the Midwest
but, uh, my wife--
she, uh...
She didn't wanna have any part of it.
Why?
Well...
Carnies are good people
but, uh--
you know, you're either
with the show or you're not.
There's-- there's nowhere
in the middle.
And if you're not with the show
then you're a mark.
You're a sucker.
And she didn't like that.
You're not gonna need the badge.
They're gonna tell you're a cop without it.
Actually, people very rarely
guess I'm a cop.
Oh, yeah. Let me do the talking.
When it's advisable.
- And don't mention Danny until I do.
- I'll be the judge of that.
Hey! No trespassing.
Fair's not open yet.
Scram.
Or else what?
Or else I'll give you a good whoppin'.
That's what else.
Uh, how about this, Pete?
If you can catch me
then I will marry that damn
ugly sister of yours.
Patrick Jane.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, man!
I heard you were police.
I didn't believe it
but here you are
with a real, live cop.
This is my good friend Teresa.
Doesn't bite.
If you're okay with Jane
I guess you're okay with me.
Thanks.
You know, I haven't
seen you a while, eh?
Well, you know.
Yeah, I know.
So what brings you here now?
- I'll give you three guesses.
- Uh, Danny?
Got it in one.
- Danny's a good boy.
- What's he been up to?
Hey, Sam.
Come on out here.
I got a surprise for you, honey.
Come on. You ready?
Oh, look at you, huh?
Yeah.
- Uh, what was that for?
- Detroit.
Oh, yeah. Fair enough.
What's with the State Trooper?
Yeah, it's, like, unreal, huh?
A Jane working with the law.
- How do I look like a cop?
- Oh, please.
Look like Cagney and Lacey
had a baby, called it Pepper.
- They're looking for Danny.
- Danny's in trouble.
Yeah, what else is new?
Danny's always in trouble.
Remember the morning
of your wedding?
Oh, yes. Yeah. My--my wife had
to bail Danny out in her dress.
She was not very happy.
Well, it's good to see you and all
but the police is the police. No offense.
None taken.
Well, Pete, wh-why don't you
take Pepper here
and, uh, show her the elephant?
- I'd love to see the elephant.
- My pleasure. Right this way.
Her name is Daisy.
She's cute.
She's a mean old girl.
She'd run down her own kids
for an apple.
No.
You think I'm kidding?
Here. Give her one.
- Where do I put it?
- In here.
You two get along
you can take her home with you.
You want another one?
What kinda trouble Danny got?
Worst kind of trouble.
Damn shame.
Not surprised though.
Danny's been heading downhill
all the way since Angela died.
There's a man
need a big sister.
- Yeah.
- So...
I should help you
and the cops find him...
Why?
Danny called me,
uh, just out of the blue
and he asked for my help.
Danny doesn't always do
what's best for his own interests.
- Tendency to outfox himself.
- True.
But he asked for my help
and that's what I'll give him.
A few hours ago, I was wiping
a murder weapon clean
in case it had Danny's fingerprints
on it.
I don't know
where Danny is now...
But Nicki does.
Talk to Biltmore Nicki.
Same gig as always.
It's good to see you.
I'm glad you're doing okay.
You are doing okay, aren't you?
Oh, yeah.
My little friend Pepper is gonna need
a ride back to the office.
She's huge.
Kinda tickles.
Hey!
Jane!
Detective Reece called three times.
He's pissed.
He can get in line.
Where's Van Pelt?
Oh, hey, boss.
Can I borrow the car?
That's funny.
Anything on Ruskin?
Uh, yeah, he's a, uh,
former escape artist.
Had an act as a kid
just like Jane, Houdini Junior.
Says he could do the water
torture cell trick at 17
which I guess is good
if you like that sort of thing.
Cho, go and talk
to the victim's wife.
See if she knows Ruskin.
Rigsby, have Van Pelt help you
look into his financials.
Look for other names.
Con men rarely work alone.
Where is Van Pelt?
Daniel Ruskin.
I don't know him. Sorry.
But you do?
I have met Daniel.
He's very charming.
- I'm sure he wouldn't hurt Landon.
- You know Ruskin?
But you told us you never heard
of his company, K-Ram.
No. I-I have no notion of his business.
I met Daniel socially...
at Landon's country club--
Murphy introduced us.
Murphy Traver?
Oh, a lovely man.
Of the Long Island Travers.
Thank you for your cooperation, Mr. Traver.
Oh, happy to talk, agents.
Yeah, I just need to get back
to this meeting in a few.
Can't trust computer nerds alone
too long, you know.
Oh, gosh.
Poor Landon. It's horrible.
So you introduced him
to Ruskin?
Yeah, yeah. Sure did.
I, uh yeah, met Daniel at the club.
He's just an outstanding guy.
But, well, why do you wanna
know about Daniel?
Well, he's a con man.
He may have killed Mr. Wale.
- You know where he is?
- Con man? Oh, my God.
My God. I invested with him.
Oh, my God.
Where's your assistant?
I'm--I'm sorry, agent.
I-I have to call my bank.
Yeah, you know, a place like this,
bunch of people
you should have an assistant.
At least a receptionist.
And with all those employees
the phone lines should be
ringing off the hook.
Landlines. So 20th-century.
No, agent. I-I'm sorry.
You c-- you're not allowed in there.
That's a clean room, agent!
Very clean.
I am having a very bad day
and you're gonna tell us
about Daniel Ruskin.
- Come on.
- Okay. All right.
My dear, sorry to bother.
Did you see two boys
run down the street?
No.
- Ma'am, what's wrong?
- I was walking to the train station
it's such a nice day--
and these two boys
just took my purse.
Ma'am, here. Come here.
Sit down.
I have to visit my sister.
She's in the hospital
in Bakersfield.
- I feel so stupid.
- That's terrible.
And the--the last train to Bakersfield
leaves in 40 minutes.
Oh, dear.
Oh. Look, uh...
Can I drive you
to the train station?
You would do that?
Oh, my dear.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sure.
"You're not taking her
anywhere, Grace."
Nice hook, Nicki.
You're such a sweet old lady.
Grace, Nicki. Nicki, Grace.
If this were for real, this old fox
would have you stripped bare.
This sweet piece of fruit
is a cop?
Damn.
- Guess I'm losing my touch.
- I'm looking for Danny.
- Look at me.
- Danny?
Look at me.
This is a family thing.
I know you know where he is.
Tell me, Nicki
or this nice piece of fruit
will take you downtown
and treat you to a complimentary
cavity search.
- Hypothetically, what happened?
- Hypothetically?
We were running "the rag".
"We'll let you invest
in a surefire stock market winner."
"It's a little illegal. Don't tell anybody.
Blah, blah."
Hypothetically...
Danny hooked Landon good.
I mean, had him begging us
to let him invest.
He was bringing us
some statue worth 200 grand.
So you and Danny killed Landon
and took the statue?
No. No. Why take it when he was
gonna give it to us in the morning?
Maybe you took it, Murphy.
You didn't wanna share with Danny
so you called Wale
and met him early.
Things got outta hand. You need
to help yourself, tell your side.
No, no, no, no.
- You're a liar.
- She's right. You are.
Where's Danny Ruskin?
You're a businessman, so's Danny.
He'll understand.
I don't know. I don't.
But I know who he's with.
Trixie... somebody.
Rich and hot.
Yeah. Danny's always got
a second revenue stream.
Always...
monetizing.
Excuse me.
Jane, where the hell are you?
"Wow. Hope that's the decaf
you're getting."
- How did you--
- "I can hear the foam machine."
Anyway, I promised Grace
I'd call, so I called.
Lovely to talk to you. Bye now.
- Put her on now.
- No, I've already ditched her.
Jane, you have to come in.
Danny could be dangerous.
We're not looking to use
deadly force, but things happen.
It's not safe for you.
Getting close to nabbing him, are you?
Oh, that's good to hear.
Well, may the best man win, Lisbon.
- Jane!
- Boss.
Checked the sign-in logs at the K-Ram
offices. Found a Trixie Mercado.
She's the daughter of the guy
who owns the building.
- She has a place in Midtown.
- Thanks.
May the best man win.
Detective Reece, it's Lisbon.
We've got a lead on Ruskin.
It's party time.
Baby, why are you packing?
God, you are killing me.
You're so gorgeous.
Seriously, uh, I'm dying
but I gotta go, baby.
Something came up.
I'll be back soon, all right?
- Danny.
- Hey.
Long time.
Danny, what the hell?
You must be, uh, Trixie, huh?
Hi. I'm--I'm Patrick.
No need to be scared.
Danny and I--we're family.
Biltmore Nicki called you, huh? And that's
it, you're just gonna hop on out of here?
- I--You're mad.
- I just got here.
You're mad. I get that. I do.
But I needed your help.
I needed your wisdom
and--and cunning and--
Yeah, how much help can I be to you
when I'm in handcuffs, Danny?
Wh-what can I say?
Calling you in was the best
of some very unsavory options.
Then tell me what happened
with Landon Wale last night--
honest and quick.
I don't have all day.
"Police, open up!'
- You son of a bitch.
- That has nothing to do with me.
"Trixie Mercado, are you in there?"
- "We've got some questions."
- Oh, please.
What the hell is going on?
Look, just talk to 'em.
I have influence.
- We can sort this thing out.
- "Ms. Mercado?"
If you didn't do anything
you got nothing to worry about.
Nothing to worry about?
I am not spending a day in jail!
Not one day.
Never again. Ever. You got me?
Ms. Mercado, open the door
right now!
Back up. I'm going in.
Give me some room.
Back up!
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Danny's not here.
Yep.
Danny went that way.
All by himself.
All units search the area.
Suspect has fled.
Establish a 2-block perimeter
around this block.
Hey. You're Patrick's friend, right?
- Yeah.
- He said to tell you
he's really, really sorry about all this.
Jane's with Danny?
Jane? No.
It was a man. Patrick.
Tell me what happened
with Landon Wale.
- Ooh, big detective.
- Consultant.
Consultant.
Stop stalling. Just tell me
if you killed the man
and I'll take you to Mexico.
I'm touched. Cabo?
- You--you'd do that for me?
- Yes, I would.
Why?
Because your sister
would want me to.
You sound like a mark.
Or you think I'm a mark.
- Which?
- You sound like you're in over your head.
Yeah, way over my head.
Not like Patrick. No.
You would never get in
way over your head, would you?
Too smart for that, never make
mistakes. Not the boy wonder.
Why won't you answer
my question?
Is it because you hate me?
Or is it because you did
in fact, kill the man?
Hate.
Why would I hate you, bro?
I asked my question first.
I didn't kill Landon.
I smell deception
but it's hard to tell with you
because you're kind of a sociopath
like all the great con men.
I am great, huh?
First compliment you ever
gave me, I can recall.
Convince me, Danny.
Come on. Try.
Just--just make me believe
that you didn't kill that guy.
You want me to dance for you?
Hmm? I should crawl for you?
Okay, that's it. I'm leaving
and I'm gonna call the cops.
They will be here
in five minutes.
I'd make yourself scarce.
Stop!
You think I won't do it?
Not sure.
But... I wouldn't blame you
if you did.
Agent Hightower.
- You lied to me.
- Detective Reece has some concerns
about the Landon Wale case.
Seems like you didn't tell him
that Jane is the brother-in-law
of Daniel Ruskin
the prime suspect.
At the time of my conversation
with Detective Reece
I didn't know
about the connection.
I apologize for the oversight.
- I'm supposed to buy that?
- No purchase required, detective.
- Where's Jane now?
- No, I don't know where he is.
You don't know where he is?
Okay.
I tell you what,
this is what I'm going to do.
I'm gonna get an arrest warrant
and I'm gonna have
every cop on the street
looking for him and Ruskin.
You need to get control
of your unit, lady.
What you have right here
is slackness.
If Mr. Jane is involved
in obstruction of justice
aiding and abetting
or anything like that
he's yours.
Are we done?
- I guess we are.
- Keep in touch.
Jane's in trouble.
Detective Rigsby.
- You wanted to talk to me?
- It's agent.
Uh, we're reinterviewing a number
of Mr. Wale's associates.
It's just routine.
Let's go to desk, shall we?
You look... different.
Yeah, it's really hot at the office.
The air's broken.
No money to fix it?
We found out that the company was
gonna file for bankruptcy, Heather.
- The place is broke.
-You should really talk to Melanie.
Yeah, but what happened
to the company?
Do you read the news?
- After you.
- Real estate's not doing so well
and Landon made a bad deal
or seven.
He was a cowboy
a win big, lose big.
Please, take a seat.
So how did, uh, Melanie and Concetta
take the bankruptcy news?
They didn't know.
Landon only told me.
I, uh, I keep the books.
So you're looking at them, huh?
We look at every place
at everybody.
Hmm.
"Hmm" meaning what?
No, nothing. It's just...
Who knew he'd be worth more
dead than alive?
- You mean life insurance?
- Uh-huh.
Thank you.
Well, this policy's less
than three months old.
- Did Mrs. Wale take it out?
- Connie?
No. She's not the beneficiary.
Melanie is.
The sister.
Well, what's it worth?
$2 million.
If you know where they are
you need to tell me.
Sac PD's got a manhunt going.
Jane and Danny
could get arrested or shot.
They're survivors.
They're gonna do okay.
- Jane will get fired from the CBI.
- Oh, no.
This job is all he has.
If he's arrested they'll take that from him.
I'm his friend. I can help.
Ms. Lisbon
they just took off.
We don't know where they went.
You swear?
I swear.
My sister...
was the only good--
clean honest thing
that I had in my life...
and you ran off with her.
You took her away from me
away from what she knew, so...
You know, yeah.
I've been mad at you.
Very mad.
I didn't--
I didn't take her away.
She didn't--she didn't want
the carny life. She hated it.
She wanted to get out.
We--we both did.
And you know how hard that is.
That was--that was our thing.
That's what we did together.
We--we--we escaped together.
Nice escape plan, bro.
- You got her killed.
- Thanks for reminding me.
Yeah, you just had
to be a big shot
had to get on the TV
and run your mouth.
It's your fault she's dead.
Yes. It is.
I know that.
It is my fault.
And I just-- I hope that one day
you will, uh, forgive me.
And maybe one day
I'll forgive myself.
- Forgive you?
- Not for my sake. For yours.
Because hating me is just a waste
of your energy. It's pointless.
Just move on. Drop it.
Find something to love.
Love?
- Man, you really have changed.
- Yeah.
I don't--
I don't know if I...
I don't require an answer, Danny.
I just...
You got something in your eye?
I got allergies. It's...
It's pollen.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Landon Wale.
Yeah, Landon.
Boy...
There's a mark.
He was so hot to get taken.
He called me that night
and wanted to move up
the action.
When I got there, he was dead.
That's it.
- I did not kill him.
- What was the action?
Landon was supposed to bring me
the gold statue--
not to give to me
just to show me, you know
to prove he had the collateral
to invest in my hedge fund coup.
And this mook
was hooked deep.
Thought he was flying to Brazil
with his hot assistant
and all the money.
Brazil, I like it.
- Old school.
- Yeah.
He had it all mapped out little place
on the beach, a fishing boat.
Perfect mark.
Hey. To suckers. Gotta love 'em.
Don't move.
Keys.
Go on.
Jane!
Jane, it's me.
Hey, Lisbon.
- Excellent work finding us.
- I am very unhappy with you.
- Is he in there?
- Yeah.
Bring him out. No funny business
or I will shoot to kill.
You're very persuasive.
We'll be right out.
Ms. Anders, thanks for coming in.
Sure. Uh, what's this about?
Uh, the insurance policy.
We, uh, have a few questions.
Policy?
Oh, for Landon. Sure.
You know, it's common to have
a key man policy
- for small businesses.
- I'm sure you can straighten things out.
We have some, uh, paperwork
to take care of.
If you could heck here
and sign here, please.
Thanks for the call, Agent Lisbon.
My pleasure. We have a deal?
Yeah, we'll forget about
your lies and incompetence.
- All right, up against the car.
- Hey, what!
- Get your hands behind your back.
- Wait. Hey.
- Hands behind the back.
- Hey!
You said we could work it out
if I came in, not him.
- I got no deal with him.
- It's for the best, Danny.
It's for the best. We've all gotta get out
from underneath it sometime.
- You bastard!
- Sorry.
God. You son of a bitch!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
- How could you do this?
- Take it easy.
I'll kill you! You betrayed me.
I will kill you!
- Did you have to be so rough with him?
- "Don't tell me how to do my job."
- I mean, your bedside--
- "You're lucky I'm not taking you in."
- All right, both of you--
- Are you threatening me?
I'm not threatening anybody.
If it weren't for me
you wouldn't even have him!
Are you delusional?
You blocked the investigation
- You spat on me.
- every step of the way.
- He spat on me!
- That's enough.
- You wanna go in with him? Say the word.
- Enough.
I'd be happy--
"This whole investigation..."
- Hey! Hey, hey! Stop!
- Lisbon! Lisbon!
Hey!
Stop! Hey!
Hi. This is police business.
Patrick Jane. I'm with the CBI.
Yes, I saw you there
- when the killer escaped.
- Yeah.
It was horrible, Connie.
Terrible story.
Yeah, well, I'd like to speak
to Ms. Wale alone, please.
It's very important.
Thank you.
This is awkward
but we have reason to believe
that Danny Ruskin has
every intention of killing you.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
He has a violent temper
and several convictions to prove it
including shooting and killing a man
ten years ago.
But why would
he wanna hurt me?
He figured it out.
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
That you killed your own husband
and in doing so
ruined Danny Ruskin's life.
What?
Mr. Jane, that's an outrageous charge.
Yes, one I almost
didn't believe myself
until meeting you just now.
Then it became glaringly obvious
you have deep-seated control issues
mixed in with jealousy
and your own weird lust
for violence.
Landon was gonna take the money
and run away with that leggy assistant.
- What's her name?
- Shut up. Landon loved me.
No, he didn't
and you know he didn't.
Hell, maybe you even knew that he was
headed off to Brazil with her
but what you didn't know, Mrs. Wale
is that Landon was being played.
He was being conned by no one
other than Danny Ruskin.
And when Landon
took your Aphrodite statue
you assumed he was
gonna give it to the mistress.
Your honeymoon gift--
the very symbol
of your love for each other.
"So you followed Landon to where
you thought he was gonna meet"
"with that statuesque strumpet"
"and you killed him."
"Then you took what you thought
was rightfully yours."
That's ridiculous.
That Ruskin character killed Landon.
Where is the statue now, Concetta?
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Wait!
"You can't go in there!"
Oh, look at this. You could land
a jumbo jet in here.
Landon wasn't big
on the, uh, subtlety, was he?
Probably why you knew
he was having an affair.
You must leave, Mr. Jane.
Right now.
You bitch.
- And you.
- Easy.
- Christmas came early this year.
- Oh, Danny, another gun?
Come on. Really?
What--just...
None of this would have happened
except for you.
- You ruined everything.
- Okay, listen. Danny...
- You don't have to do this.
- Shut up!
Okay, listen to me.
You're not this person.
- Okay? You're not this person. Look--
- You backstabbed me!
I trusted you.
You think I'm a mark?
You think you can run games on me?
Oh. Oh, my God.
You shot me, Danny.
Son of a bitch.
What'd you do that for?
- Oh, my God.
- Patrick.
Bastard.
No.
No. No, no, no, no.
Stay with me.
Stay with me. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You made me shoot him.
No, no. No, please.
- This is your fault.
- No.
This is your fault! God!
You ruined my life!
You deserve this, bitch.
Your ruined my life.
I could've had everything!
Okay, I can fix it!
I'll fix it. I swear.
Money.
So much money, you can go to Switzerland.
You can go anywhere you want.
- Yeah?
- You don't have to kill me.
Look, I can prove it.
Yeah? Go!
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
This is worth a lot of money.
Take it.
It's yours. Take it!
Connie, Connie, Connie.
You fell for the oldest gag in the book.
Huh?
And one of the cheapest--
$3.55 at a novelty store near you.
Beats the hell outta the cackle bladder.
- You got a little...
- A li--a little...
Kind of minty.
How are my teeth?
They're good?
That was great, huh?
Concetta Wale, you're under arrest.
Turn around. Put your hands
behind your back.
- Turn around.
- I'll take that.
You...
Come on. Let's go.
Sac PD wanna talk to you
about Landon Wale and K-Ram.
There are some
fraud charges pending.
Fraud is very hard to prove
especially when nothing
changed hands.
In fact, now I think of it
I'm actually innocent here.
Whatever. They're on their way.
I believe she's telling you
to scram.
That's not what I said.
- Thank you, Lisbon.
- I didn't hear that.
Thank you, Lisbon.
I can't hear anything.
So...
This is it, huh?
It's nice.
Classy.
They'd like it, I guess
if they had a preference.
You know, this is
the first time I've been here
since the funeral.
Why is that?
Because they're not here.
Hey, who knows for sure? Maybe they're up
there right now looking down at us.
You know, Annie's saying
"Lighten up, you dummies."
Yeah, maybe.
I'm sorry I asked to come.
Who knew a trip to the cemetery
would be such a downer?
Sorry. It's irrational.
No reason to be sad.
You gonna give 'em
those flowers or what?
Guilt is for marks.
You know that, right?
Yeah.